

# victor smart

WEB DEVELOPER

- 12 crest St., onitsha, anambra state
- https://vicprof.herokuapp.com/

#### PROFILE

A passionate web developer with flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time. passionate about building world class web development projects.

I design and develop userfriendly websites such as Elearning platform, Eecommerce website, voting platform, instant messaging web app, chatbots, blogs, portfolio etc.

I help businesses with conversion-led website, that guarantee high profile page view user experience and improve sale through automations.

### SKILLS

Python/Django/Bootstrap

.....

Html/Css/ReactJS/Javascript

Nodejs/ExpressJS/MongoDB

creativity

000000

teamwork

.....

problem solving

.....

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER**

may 2020 - Present

creator

- establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantee high profile page view user experience.
- design, develop and document E-commerce inventory web app with vendor management dashboard, product tracking, reporting tools, product categorization, mobile support etc. with Django and React.js.
- responsible for fullstack web development for all cleint projects.
- created a website and facebook-linked blog for local client.
- passionate about building word class web applications.
- increase customer satisfaction by 35% and customer retention by 30%.

#### WEB DEVELOPER

apr 2019 - jun 2020

creator

- · built an ecommerce webapp to sell product online .
- develop a customer web form for a local dentist's office increase patient satisfaction scores by 30%.
- deliver a presentation on "web development best practices" at a meet up.
  - cultivate excellent relationship with client that lead to a strong base of referral businesses.

#### **CLASSROOM TEACHER**

# ASAF college

may 2016 - mar 2019

- accomplished classroom teacher, with year of experience teaching large class of student with proven ability to teach both small and large groups.
- establish positive relationship with student and effective communication with emphasis on skills acquisition and individual growth.

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Bachelor's Degree in Physics

mar 2014 - aug 2018

university of nigeria nsukka

- University of Nigeria Nsukka, Bachelor's degree (university degree) in Education Physics/Education